Hello everyone, today I will show you how to make a four-core buckle.
First of all, the four-core buckle is divided into a combined state and an open state.
Here we will first explain the four-core buckle in a combined state.
Let's take the front door handle as an example.
You can see that the corresponding board also has a four-core buckle.
First of all, we use the hook and loop tool to hook the circle of the buckle into the inner line or shape.
Then use the sewing tool to sew them together.
Open the simulation.
In this way, we can simulate a four-core buckle in a combined state.
Next, we see the surface of the door handle.
If our four-core buckle does not have a face buckle, we need to hide the trace of the sewing line.
Here we can use the editor sewing line tool to select the sewing line just added and change its hair line strength to 0.
In this way, we have a four-core buckle without a face buckle.
If we have a face buckle, we need to use the add button tool to add a button to the door handle.
In the right side of the door handle, we select the added button to modify its shape, size and material.
Its color, surface light intensity, reflection intensity, etc. can be modified.
Next, let's rotate the view.
You can see that there is still a gap between the button and the clothing fabric.
Here we use the select button.
In this way, we can use the select move button tool.
Select this button in front of us.
Then, in the right side of the door handle, change the length of the line to a negative value.
Let our button stick to our fabric.
At the same time, we also need to close the gap between the button and the fabric of the door handle in the door handle.
To avoid a conflict between the button and the fabric when we simulate.
This is our door handle.
This is how we make a four-box button in the collection state.
Next, let's see how the four-box button works.
The face button is still the same method.
If there is no face button, we can skip this step.
Next, let's add the purple button and the mother button.
You can see that the purple button should be added on the reverse side of the door handle.
The mother button is on the collar.
We find the body window.
In the button button column, click on the add two default buttons.
Then, name them separately as the purple button and the mother button.
Next, we choose the purple button.
Use the add button tool to add it to our door handle.
The position of our face button is the same.
Next, we switch the tool to the select move button tool.
Select the two buttons that we just added.
Then, click on the right button to find the flip button.
Flip them to the reverse side of our fabric.
Then, in the body window, we select the current purple button.
To modify their shape, size and material.
In the same way, let's make the mother button.
Next, we use the top button to adjust its height.
Finally, let's get the button button to adjust the length of the button.
Let them stick to the surface of our fabric.
Turn off the conflict of button button.
To prevent a conflict of button button in the later simulation.
Continue to increase the perspective of the button button.
This is the production method of our four-core code.